I got a bunch of new things from Amorese. Lots of spandex items, new catsuit designs, new colors.
So it's going to be a lot of different outfits. I'm going to start right away.
I'm starting with the Inferna catsuit. It is available in multiple colors and my Patreons decided that I should try silver.
So here I am. The new thing is that we have this round neckline here and it's super easy to get dressed with that
because it's really stretchy and you can just dress it very fast because it's very wide
we have no zipper as you can see here neither in the back nor in the front
again getting into this is very easy gloves are integrated socks are integrated I'm wearing size
large and it's asian sizing so watch out for that check out the size charts I'd say it's really long
I have other Amoresi suits which are shorter and this feels especially in the arms rather long long enough. The legs are a bit too short for me but as the fabric is really stretchy I can pull it up and a good thing is it stays up because it's a catsuit.
Of course you know me, Kosa, okay, but I love black. So here is the same catsuit in black. I'm packing it for the first time and you can see again how stretchy this neck is. So getting into it is no problem at all.
So here we are, this is the black one. It's very slippery so I can slide around here because of the very soft spandex fabric. And again I have to say the arms are really long. The legs are shorter for me at least in my proportions.
well yeah it's as always the nice one because it's black the thing about
spandex being slippery is I noticed that open heels like peep toes or something
are not the wisest choice because I tend to slide a lot in the heels and slide
down so I prefer to wear closed heels with spandex I also got this belt back
or as a belt and a detachable belt. Rather it's a belt and a detachable back.
So I'm wearing the back here and I'm gonna put this on this side. Does it look like something when I wear it on the front?
I don't know. Maybe. I think I prefer it in the back like this.
So a little bit of styling for this one also. It's great that the heels are not
sporting any silver or gold but gunmetal grey so it's all all black look except
for the logo and I can also try to put a jacket on it let's see how that looks
got this one from my needlework
now I look like I want to go skiing
I think it's okay I think I would get rid of the belt back to be honest
because the jacket is a lot
and it has a sleeker look this way I can also try and close it
Something like that. Or maybe close the lower part. Looks kind of cozy with the wool part here.
And yeah, not too bad. All right, this was the black one. I do have other catsuits
and other colors, so let's continue. So it's the Celestia front suit catsuit in the color
Acid Lime. I've got this catsuit multiple times already. My favorite one is
some that kind of dark gray, galmashel gray, and I thought let's try out the new color.
It's really really
crazy and this is going to be the craziest color in the whole video, so
yeah
Fun and the zipper is even brighter so that I can also open the zipper.
I prefer it because I love front zips because of this. I say it's a bit shorter
than the Inferna catsuit I've worn before, the other model. It feels shorter
in the body part so the torso length and also in the arms of course I don't have
gloves here to pull the arms down. It's still very very stretchy so you can
definitely squeeze into it but still have a look at the size chart and order the size you really
need and nothing too small because if you squeeze into a suit that is way too small then of course
it will rip or the zipper will break so choose wisely same catsuit but different material so
this is actually the sheer version of this catsuit don't get confused yes I know the one before was
also slightly see-through but this one is a different fabric so I noticed it's thinner and
it stretches more so this actually fits me better because it's a bit longer and yeah the sheer
option this is pink yarrow and there's also turquoise available or turquoise I don't know
this is a word I can't I have no idea how to pronounce it's German anyway I do have matching
gloves for this one so same color same material but gloves let me close the zipper first because
I know that with gloves I can't really do it properly so these are one size because they're
really stretchy and should fit most hands and wrists for me they're a bit too wide
but my wrists are really thin anyway here we go I have more colors to go
I'm going to change. So this is the Ateniti suit. It's a mesh catsuit and it's actually
not by Amoresi but by their sub-brand Amoti. They usually do sheer catsuits made of nylon. I have
a separate video about Amoti products you can check out and I decided to try this one because
it's new and it's not a nylon fabric but as I said some kind of mesh so it's not as stretchy
as the nylon or spandex catsuits it's a bit stretchy but not too much so you should keep
that in mind and we have these nice seams here this is it from behind and there's also print
here in the area of my collarbone. I am going to try and layer these and put the Inferna
kit suit on top of this one because I think it can be a nice look with the black mesh part
under the dark red color.
Okay.
all right here we go and yes as I thought this looks really nice looks like I don't know some
kind of long sleeve underneath but it's the catsuit looks very elegant with the combination
with a dark wine red color. I like it very much. And it feels grown up to have this mesh part here.
So there are so many colors available you should definitely check out the Amoretti... Amoretti...
There are so many colors available you should definitely check out the Amoresi and Amoti
webshops and have a look yourself i do have a discount code you should use that to get a few
percent off and then i'd say happy shopping because it's so much fun to choose from all the colors
and all the different designs pay attention to the sizing chart again as i said i'm wearing
size large and everything because it's asian sizing and let me know in the comments which
one was your favorite outfit I think actually this one is mine with the mesh part here so yeah
I hope you enjoyed this video check out my other videos I do have more Amorese and Amote videos
and leave a thumbs up subscribe to my channel check out my patreon see you in the next video bye